http://www.harrywalker.com/content/hwa-privacy-policy-page

Toggle navigation
Toggle Search
CONTACT US     646.227.4900
My Speaker List ()
My Speaker List ()
646.227.4900
Find Your Speaker:
|
VIEW {{pagination.pageMaxLen == HWA.defPageSize ? HWA.defPageSize : "ALL"}}
|
VIEW {{pagination.pageMaxLen == HWA.defPageSize ? HWA.defPageSize : "ALL"}}
We're here to help!
CONTACT AN AGENT
646.227.4900
646.227.4900
Customize your search to findideal speakers for upcoming events
discover speakers by
Keyword
Topicwhat they talk about
Typewho they are and what they do
Need a bit of assistance?Don't worry, we're here to help.
CONTACT AN AGENT
CONTACT AN AGENT
Oops! Adjust your search filtersto see more speakers.
Need a bit of assistance?Don't worry, we're here to help.
CONTACT AN AGENT
CONTACT AN AGENT
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for www.harrywalker.com. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about speakers or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You can do the following at any time by emailing info@harrywalker.com
See what data we have about you, if any
Change/ correct any data we have about you
Have us delete any data we have about you
Opt-out of future promotional communications. Note that if you opt-out of promotional communications, we may still communicate with you about non-promotional communications
In the cases where we use a third-party social media platform, you can opt out by changing your settings on that platform.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Cookies
We use "cookies" on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor's hard drive to improve access to and experience of our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.
Website Forms
When submitting a form from our website, you give HWA permission to maintain the contact information you provided as a means of contacting you in the future.  Where required by applicable law, we will only send you promotional communications with your prior consent.
Links
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.
Updates
Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately at info@harrywalker.com.
About the HWA Speakers Bureau  |  HWA Exclusive Speakers  |  HWA New Speakers  |  Get Event Ideas  |  How to Book A Speaker
